Okay, so because you
don't have an email
system set up yet,
we're going to build
you a very simple
one. And really our
goal is to get
your list to 300
people before we even
bother sending them a
single email, as there's
not really a huge
amount of point sending
a weekly newsletter at
this stage. So we're
going to keep this
as simple as possible.
And here's what your
MVP, minimum viable email
system version is going
to look like. You're
going to create a
signup page of a
simple form. Then anyone
who signs that form
will get tagged. So
they're saved to your
email list. And then
you will just automatically,
with your software, send
a welcome email that
delivers a welcome and
a soft pitch. That
is literally all we're
going to do right
now. I did this
exact thing for years,
nothing more fancy, and
it got me to
like $60 ,000 a
month. So you don't
need to overthink this
right now. This is
our first step in
you collecting emails. And
later, once you have
more people on that
list, we're going to
build bigger systems. So
like I said, we're
not going to email
these people regularly until
you've got around 300
subscribers on the list.
And you don't even
need to send a
week or any email
to this list. We
just want to collect
them right now. All
right. So once you
hit that number, that's
when we start adding
more nurture emails and
scaling your system. Now,
you're going to need
an email platform to
make this work, but
don't overthink it. They
all pretty much do
the same thing. So
here's a few options.
People use GoHighLevel. More
advanced, perfect if you
have or you want
a sales team later.
ActiveCampaign, it's very good
for email. It's like
a specialist in that,
but it can get
expensive fast. Kajabi and
Kartra. Lots of my
clients use Kajabi. Kajabi.
You also want like
a course hosting and
funnel pages built in.
Both of those will
probably fit your needs.
I use Kartra. It's
a little bit clunky,
but I've had it
for five, six years
now. To be honest,
it doesn't matter which
one you get started.
They're all as bad
as each other for
different reasons. The goal
is to get you
moving, not to spend
hours hunting for this
perfect tool. So the
first thing you need
on your signup page
is just a headline.
The headline just needs
to set up the
benefit of joining in
a very short sentence,
like explode your profits
with less work, or
boost your personal brand
and internet fame with
my next level strategies.
Now, because we're not
going to email it
every week to start
or hardly at all,
don't say we're going
to do it weekly.
And if you're struggling,
use the AI prompt
I've got, where you
say the reader of
my emails want to
insert the big goal,
and their biggest problem
is insert the problem.
Write five short landing
page headlines to encourage
them to sign up.
And really the format
that we can use
is get result they
want without problem they
have. Then we want
a sub headline. It's
just support. It supports
the main headline. And
all it needs to
do is address potential
objections. So you could
say, you know, join
fitness fanatics shaving hours
off batch producing their
weekly gym food with
my previously unreleased tips.
Something like that. So
I've got another AI
prompt, which you can
just copy and paste,
and I'll leave it
below the video, and
you can help it
get you, and it
will help pick you
a sub headline. But
after that, all we
then want is a
form with a name,
an email. And that
is it. We don't
want anything more right
now. Just as simple
as possible. And then
in the welcome email,
you simply say hello.
Thank you for signing
up. As soon as
I have something incredibly
useful for you that
will help you achieve
whatever the result they
signed up for, I'll
send it straight to
your inbox. P .S.
If you're serious about
solving whatever the problem
they signed up for
is, click this link
to learn more how
I can help you
accelerate that. Basically, it's
hi, welcome. Thanks for
signing up. I'll send
you stuff based on
what you signed up
for. P .S. Call
to action. Work with
me. Just keep it
very short, very simple.
Only a few lines,
and that is all.
And don't expect a
huge amount from this
right now. It's just
the basics to get
us going. Because once
we've really, all we
want is that email
list built, so that
when it hits 300,
and we do start
sending emails more often,
promoting to it, we
can get some sales
kind of straight away.
So that's it. You're
going to pick a
tool. Then you're going
to build the signup
page, and you're going
to add the welcome
email, which I've put
a template below. Just
fill it out and
adapt it to yourself.
Then you're going to
link that below every
video, and in your
About Us, along with
your offer. And we
can move on fast.
In phase seven, we
might want to come
back and revisit this.